Transcription by CastingWords
CastingWords
The Eurasian continent was attacked by a massive spatial quake.
There were 150 million victims of this unprecedented event.
And now...
The Eurasian continent was attacked by a massive city.
I don't know.
But here...
We'll be right back.
round by ourselves
It's a nagging media
Ok this way!
We hope you will see if we can't breathe in John's face
This will still be guardians
Don't you even know how to show whether it is a sound
Carry on undays 2021
Noes in diseased world
copies hundreds of years
A personal humility
That's pretty funny questions
Wake up!
My little sister is giving me what could possibly be the worst wake-up call ever.
Godry, darling little sister of mine.
What is it, darling big brother of mine?
Get off of me! You're too big!
Ow!
Sorry, did that hurt? I bet you're awake, though.
Hey! Don't just go right back to sleep! Wake up! Come on, wake up, sleepyhead! Wake up!
Listen to me. Run away.
I've contracted the mysterious ten more minutes of sleep or else my sister goes to tickle hell virus.
Often referred to as the T-Virus for short.
What? You've got what?
Run away, Kotry. Run! Well, I can still control myself.
Wait! But then what's going to happen to you, bro?
As long as you're safe, it doesn't matter what happens to me. Run away.
No, I can't! I can't leave you!
Okay. Much better.
I don't want to go to tickle hell. Someone help me!
It's me! Calm down. It's only me.
What? Are you sure?
I am much good friend to you. Yes, my kotori big brother.
A spatial quake was recorded early this morning near the center of Tengu City.
There was only slight damage, with no casualties among residents in the area.
Investigations continue as to the cause of the spatial quake.
Again? Sounded close, too.
It was.
Spatial quakes. Widespread vibration phenomena.
An area randomly starts vibrating, and no one knows why.
These quakes are irrational, mysterious, and unbelievably destructive.
After the massive catastrophe 30 years ago,
spatial quakes continued around the world for six terrifying months.
In Japan, the great southern Kanto spatial quake completely flattened an area not too far from our house.
It was total devastation.
In the 25 years after that, nothing happened.
Nothing.
Until five years ago, when a spatial quake showed up in the redeveloped Tengu City.
Not long after that, we started hearing about quakes all the time.
Most of which occurred here, in Japan.
It's weird.
There have been a lot lately.
You're telling me.
This is happening earlier than planned.
Hold it!
No sweets!
Seriously!
Just make sure you eat breakfast, okay?
Uh-huh!
Okay, bro.
I love you!
Oh, hey.
Got any requests for lunch?
Oh, yeah!
One deluxe kids' plate!
Whee!
That's from a diner menu.
We don't serve that dish at this restaurant.
Come on!
Oh, please!
Pretty please!
Put the cherry on top.
It's yummy!
Deluxe kids' plate wins!
I love eating out for lunch.
It's a diner.
Not that exciting.
Yuh-huh!
Thank you so much, bro!
Okay, so after school, I'll be waiting for you right here in front of the restaurant.
Sounds good.
And don't break your promise!
Be here no matter what happens.
Even if the place is taken over by terrorists, we'll still eat!
If that goes down, I doubt they'll let us stay.
I'll be here.
Be careful on your way to school.
Hey, isn't that Shido-Itsuka?
Do they seem too close?
Because I've heard he's got a weird sister complex.
That's so lame.
Don't forget, you promised me, so I'm going to be here ready to eat even if a spatial quake happens.
Sweet.
Now go to school already.
Well, hey there.
What's up?
Hey, Tonomachi.
You ready for the semester?
You sure look like you are.
Oh, have you also heard the rumors about him?
Yeah, he swings both ways, as they say.
That's so lame.
Are you okay, Ai?
I'm perfect.
I just saw a super genius creep in.
That's so lame.
Nice coincidence, huh, Shido?
Lucky you being put in the same class with me again.
Some people would call this fate.
I would be one of those people.
Of course you would.
Hold on.
Excuse me.
It's my girl.
What?
A girl like girlfriend?
Oh, yeah.
You want to meet her?
Check it out.
That's a dating sim.
Yeah, so what?
Doesn't change the fact that she's my girlfriend.
Don't judge me.
A dating sim will tell you everything you need to know about how to treat women.
It's like a textbook for lovin'.
This particular app is groovy because she lives on the floor.
Shido Itsuka.
Who?
Me?
Yes.
How do you know my name?
You mean you don't remember?
Hey, who is she?
Am I supposed to know her?
Of course you are.
That is Origami Tobiichi, otherwise known as the super genius.
For real?
Crazy.
She knows me?
That chick always has some of the best grades in our class.
She's ridiculous at sports, and I mean, look at her.
Gorgeous.
On my girls I probably ought to have as a girlfriend list, she's never been out of the top three.
Like, ever.
How do you not know one of the most popular kids in our school?
But more importantly, why in the world does Origami know who you are?
I wish I knew, but I have no idea.
Yeah.
Oh, heck yeah.
It's Tom eyes.
It's Miss Okamine, please.
Now, quiet down.
I'll be your homeroom teacher this year.
I hope you guys are ready to learn.
Origami Tobiichi.
Why does she know who I am?
And why is she looking at me?
So weird.
What the heck is going on?
Come on.
Hey, Shido.
Want to go home together?
Sorry.
I don't got plans.
Oh, yeah?
Is it a girl?
Technically.
It's just coterie, though.
Oh, I understand.
Besides, as far as I know, there's not a girl in this school with a sensitive and kind
enough spirit to have lunch with you.
Thanks, but that was not a compliment.
Your attention, please.
This is not a drill.
On a drill.
A spatial quake.
Another one?
We need to evacuate.
The shelter near the school should be safe enough.
I repeat.
There have been a precursory signs with an impending spatial quake.
Where is she going?
Contriella.
Aura, Abu, you're a teammate's club.
Intensi, Terro, Foto, Shigelsa, Tori, Konma, Fence.
Monster Machinihi Princess.
Ah, she's here.
I repeat.
There have been a precursory signs with an impending spatial quake as a vicinity.
Leave that way to the nearest shelter immediately.
This is not a drill.
I repeat.
There have been a precursory signs with an impending spatial quake as a vicinity.
Leave that way to the nearest shelter immediately.
Everyone, please calm down and don't forget your 3Ds.
Don't push, don't run, don't walk, wait.
You might want to take it down a skosh.
Of course, you're right.
I'm sorry.
I hope Coterie is evacuating like she should.
Surely she's not still going to try to meet me at the diner.
I'll be here even if a spatial quake happens.
Come on.
Please don't be waiting in front of that diner.
She has to have gone to a shelter.
She's fine.
She's gotta be fine.
I bet the shelter she's in just has bad reception.
She has her phone on silent or something.
Let me check her location.
Just in case.
No!
Hey!
Wait!
Shino!
Okay, bro.
I love you!
Why?
Thank you so much, bro!
Why did she not just take shelter?
The city's about to be destroyed and she's worried about a promise?
Coterie!
Whoa!
What was that?
It's... a girl.
What's she doing?
Not you, too.
I see.
So it's true.
You came here to kill me.
do not try denying you are here to kill me i must deal with you before the others arrive
wait just wait please that's it's not why i came here what i i could never kill anybody
is that what you're here for
why do they not realize the futility of their attacks
this isn't just any girl
she's that strong
why does she look so sad
so
is
is everyone
enjoying
day two
of the
new semester
well
I am
because
today
we have
a brand
new
assistant
homeroom
teacher
with us
I'm
Reina
Murasame
and I'm
excited
to be
here
how
how did you
tell me
what's going
on
please
miss
Murasame
you can
just call
me Reina
Kei
Shin
my name
is
Shido
is that
right
wow
sorry
Shin
my bad
you can't
be serious
come on
you didn't even
try getting
it right
it's more
convenient
for me
to keep
close to
you
if I'm a
member
of the
school's
teaching staff
and you
should have
been able
to figure
that much
out on
your own
try not
to be
so stupid
hey
why don't
you tell
me
why you're
even
here
don't you
have
school
I got
permission
to come
today
fine
so are
you finally
gonna explain
to me
what this
training
is for
or what
it'll start
to make
more sense
once you
start using
the training
software
hit it
Reina
huh
this is
a dating
sim
Todomachi
was playing
it
no it's
not
take another
look
my
little
shito
so
about
and
so